<?xml version="1.0"?>
<MadHatterBot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <BotType>MadHatterBot</BotType>
  <MessageProfile xsi:type="SimpleCustomBotProfile">
    <TradeAmountErrors>true</TradeAmountErrors>
    <Activation>true</Activation>
    <OrderExecution>false</OrderExecution>
    <PositionSwitch>true</PositionSwitch>
  </MessageProfile>
  <IsBacktesting>false</IsBacktesting>
  <GUID>45e8ea89-48dd-4cf1-bcfa-7004b1ff5793</GUID>
  <Name>00: EOS Pump  (2)</Name>
  <AccountId>ddc2187b-da39-49b0-bfac-a507cf91385c</AccountId>
  <PriceMarket>
    <PriceSource>21</PriceSource>
    <ContractName />
    <PrimaryCurrency>EOS</PrimaryCurrency>
    <SecondaryCurrency>USDT</SecondaryCurrency>
  </PriceMarket>
  <Leverage>1</Leverage>
  <CurrentFeePercentage>0.2</CurrentFeePercentage>
  <SettlementDate>0</SettlementDate>
  <ProfitLabel>USDT</ProfitLabel>
  <Activated>false</Activated>
  <ActivatedSince>1528578000</ActivatedSince>
  <DeactivatedSince>1528593180</DeactivatedSince>
  <StatusPriceSourceOk>true</StatusPriceSourceOk>
  <StatusAccountOk>true</StatusAccountOk>
  <OpenOrdersOk>true</OpenOrdersOk>
  <WalletOk>false</WalletOk>
  <OpenOrderId />
  <TotalFeeCosts>3.0800950</TotalFeeCosts>
  <TotalProfits>0.0</TotalProfits>
  <ROI>-0.4232</ROI>
  <LastPriceUpdate>13.76840000</LastPriceUpdate>
  <ContractValue>1</ContractValue>
  <LastUpdateTime>1528594507</LastUpdateTime>
  <GroupName>4abdebf5-e5c8-4968-95c8-7af230164fd0</GroupName>
  <Notes />
  <CustomTemplate>LOCKEDLIMITORDERGUID</CustomTemplate>
  <BotLogBook>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4698 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4455 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.45 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.45 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4647 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4629 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4457 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4118 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4357 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4134 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4118 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.39 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4317 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4317 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.37 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4085 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3803 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4052 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4384 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4558 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4322 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4116 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4217 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4105 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4124 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4102 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3945 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4092 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4178 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4738 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4169 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3956 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4123 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3982 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3947 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3946 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3946 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3946 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3946 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4208 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4248 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4208 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.41 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4002 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3982 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3812 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.385 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.41 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.41 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3761 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.36 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.393 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.39 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3765 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3936 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3637 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3637 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3924 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3924 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3847 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3784 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3541 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3108 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3171 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3326 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3338 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3407 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3271 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3217 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3407 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3328 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.387 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3693 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3553 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4344 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3914 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3972 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4162 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4154 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4235 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4038 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4036 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.42 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.43 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.423 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4262 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.44 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4548 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4273 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4282 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.44 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4298 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4306 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4084 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4092 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4229 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4045 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3768 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3902 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.4046 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3739 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3908 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3657 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3504 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.353 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.35 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.35 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.3245 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.2 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1972 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1521 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.181 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.16 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1309 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.168 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1707 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1735 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1522 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.16 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1559 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1454 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.1173 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0771 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0425 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.05 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.021 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0211 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.9897 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0025 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0065 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.025 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.03 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0214 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.0301 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 14.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.9708 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.9708 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.935 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.944 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.9277 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8492 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8463 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8234 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8333 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8001 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7851 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8304 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8458 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8433 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8612 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8632 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8611 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8636 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8619 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.86 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8568 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.83 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8462 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8855 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8847 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8747 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8699 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8697 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8462 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8651 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7667 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.75 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.71 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7655 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7866 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7255 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7271 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.6424 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.6548 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.62 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.6199 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.6691 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8193 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7598 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7851 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.8003 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be above 14.635506 USDT. Current price: 13.7827 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Backtest Results:</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM ============================</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Applied Fee Percentage: 0.2%</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Total Profits: 0.0 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Total Fee Costs: 3.0800950 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Total Gain: -3.0800950 USDT</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Return On Investment: -0.4232</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM ============================</string>
    <string>6/10/2018 3:35:08 AM Bot settings saved.</string>
  </BotLogBook>
  <CompletedOrders>
    <BaseOrder xsi:type="ExchangeOrder">
      <OrderId>3a34b946-fae6-41c4-b2ea-6cc092fd59c1</OrderId>
      <OrderStatus>Completed</OrderStatus>
      <OrderStatusAsString>Completed</OrderStatusAsString>
      <OrderType>Sell</OrderType>
      <OrderTypeAsString>Sell</OrderTypeAsString>
      <PriceType>Limit</PriceType>
      <PriceTypeAsString>Limit</PriceTypeAsString>
      <Amount>53</Amount>
      <AmountFilled>0.0</AmountFilled>
      <Price>14.5669</Price>
      <FeePercentage>0.2</FeePercentage>
      <FeeCosts>1.5440914</FeeCosts>
      <Profits>0.0</Profits>
      <Notes />
      <Origin />
      <DependsOn />
      <IsExecutingAsId />
      <AddedTime>2018-06-09T20:56:00</AddedTime>
      <UnixAddedTime>1528577760</UnixAddedTime>
      <LastUpdate>2018-06-09T20:56:00</LastUpdate>
      <UnixLastUpdate>1528577760</UnixLastUpdate>
      <TimeoutInMinutes>15</TimeoutInMinutes>
      <Platform>Sandbox</Platform>
      <Pair>
        <PrimaryCurrency>EOS</PrimaryCurrency>
        <SecondaryCurrency>USDT</SecondaryCurrency>
      </Pair>
    </BaseOrder>
    <BaseOrder xsi:type="ExchangeOrder">
      <OrderId>5d00ed17-2801-42f2-af9c-6fb7c82123a6</OrderId>
      <OrderStatus>Completed</OrderStatus>
      <OrderStatusAsString>Completed</OrderStatusAsString>
      <OrderType>Buy</OrderType>
      <OrderTypeAsString>Buy</OrderTypeAsString>
      <PriceType>Limit</PriceType>
      <PriceTypeAsString>Limit</PriceTypeAsString>
      <Amount>53</Amount>
      <AmountFilled>0.0</AmountFilled>
      <Price>14.4906</Price>
      <FeePercentage>0.2</FeePercentage>
      <FeeCosts>1.5360036</FeeCosts>
      <Profits>0.0</Profits>
      <Notes />
      <Origin />
      <DependsOn />
      <IsExecutingAsId />
      <AddedTime>2018-06-09T21:26:00</AddedTime>
      <UnixAddedTime>1528579560</UnixAddedTime>
      <LastUpdate>2018-06-09T21:26:00</LastUpdate>
      <UnixLastUpdate>1528579560</UnixLastUpdate>
      <TimeoutInMinutes>15</TimeoutInMinutes>
      <Platform>Sandbox</Platform>
      <Pair>
        <PrimaryCurrency>EOS</PrimaryCurrency>
        <SecondaryCurrency>USDT</SecondaryCurrency>
      </Pair>
    </BaseOrder>
  </CompletedOrders>
  <IsOrderStopLossActive>false</IsOrderStopLossActive>
  <PlatformType>SpotTrading</PlatformType>
  <CoinPosition>Bought</CoinPosition>
  <FundsPosition>NoPosition</FundsPosition>
  <CurrentTradeAmount>53</CurrentTradeAmount>
  <CorrectedTradeAmount>0</CorrectedTradeAmount>
  <LastBuyPrice>14.4906</LastBuyPrice>
  <LastSellPrice>14.5669</LastSellPrice>
  <CappedSeconds>5</CappedSeconds>
  <Interval>2</Interval>
  <StopLoss>0</StopLoss>
  <StopLossPrice>0.001577862</StopLossPrice>
  <DisableAfterStopLoss>false</DisableAfterStopLoss>
  <PriceChangeToBuy>0</PriceChangeToBuy>
  <PriceChangeToSell>1</PriceChangeToSell>
  <PriceChangeTarget>14.635506</PriceChangeTarget>
  <Macd>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>2</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Sell</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Fast</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>6</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Slow</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>81</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Signal</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>7</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <MacdFast>6</MacdFast>
    <MacdSlow>81</MacdSlow>
    <MacdSign>7</MacdSign>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </Macd>
  <BBands>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>2</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Stay</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Length</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>1</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>21</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Dev.Up</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0.00001</Min>
        <Max>999.9</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,2})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.01</Step>
        <Value>1</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Dev.Down</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0.00001</Min>
        <Max>999.9</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,2})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.01</Step>
        <Value>1</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MA Type</Title>
        <FieldType>optionlist</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>Sma</Value>
        <Options>
          <string>Sma</string>
          <string>Ema</string>
          <string>Wma</string>
          <string>Dema</string>
          <string>Tema</string>
          <string>Trima</string>
          <string>Kama</string>
          <string>Mama</string>
          <string>T3</string>
        </Options>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Deviation</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>0</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Require FCC</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Reset Middle</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Allow Mid Sells</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <Length>21</Length>
    <Devup>1</Devup>
    <Devdn>1</Devdn>
    <MaType>Sma</MaType>
    <ResetMid>false</ResetMid>
    <AllowMidSell>false</AllowMidSell>
    <RequireFcc>false</RequireFcc>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </BBands>
  <Rsi>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>2</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Stay</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Length</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>1</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>12</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Buy level</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>100</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,1})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.1</Step>
        <Value>14</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Sell level</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>100</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,1})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.1</Step>
        <Value>84</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <RsiLength>12</RsiLength>
    <RsiOversold>14</RsiOversold>
    <RsiOverbought>84</RsiOverbought>
    <Rsi>45.6354276202075</Rsi>
    <LastRsi>45.9287721788858</LastRsi>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </Rsi>
  <UseTwoSignals>true</UseTwoSignals>
</MadHatterBot>