<?xml version="1.0"?>
<MadHatterBot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <BotType>MadHatterBot</BotType>
  <MessageProfile xsi:type="SimpleCustomBotProfile">
    <TradeAmountErrors>true</TradeAmountErrors>
    <Activation>true</Activation>
    <OrderExecution>false</OrderExecution>
    <PositionSwitch>true</PositionSwitch>
  </MessageProfile>
  <IsBacktesting>false</IsBacktesting>
  <GUID>f9f3a936-0a6d-4b93-9c5e-5461b5a6e18a</GUID>
  <Name>C: BTC CONS (2)</Name>
  <AccountId>ddc2187b-da39-49b0-bfac-a507cf91385c</AccountId>
  <PriceMarket>
    <PriceSource>21</PriceSource>
    <ContractName />
    <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
    <SecondaryCurrency>USDT</SecondaryCurrency>
  </PriceMarket>
  <Leverage>1</Leverage>
  <CurrentFeePercentage>0</CurrentFeePercentage>
  <SettlementDate>0</SettlementDate>
  <ProfitLabel>USDT</ProfitLabel>
  <Activated>false</Activated>
  <ActivatedSince>1528218737</ActivatedSince>
  <DeactivatedSince>1528305137</DeactivatedSince>
  <StatusPriceSourceOk>true</StatusPriceSourceOk>
  <StatusAccountOk>true</StatusAccountOk>
  <OpenOrdersOk>true</OpenOrdersOk>
  <WalletOk>false</WalletOk>
  <OpenOrderId />
  <TotalFeeCosts>0</TotalFeeCosts>
  <TotalProfits>0.0</TotalProfits>
  <ROI>0</ROI>
  <LastPriceUpdate>7529.03000000</LastPriceUpdate>
  <ContractValue>1</ContractValue>
  <LastUpdateTime>1528305136</LastUpdateTime>
  <GroupName>4abdebf5-e5c8-4968-95c8-7af230164fd0</GroupName>
  <Notes />
  <CustomTemplate>LOCKEDLIMITORDERGUID</CustomTemplate>
  <BotLogBook>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628.62 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628.55 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7629.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7623.75 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630.88 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7629.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.46 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.53 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7634.85 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.63 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.2 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.68 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.7 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7637.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7638 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.42 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.07 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.82 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.3 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.66 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628.1 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632.26 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630.02 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632.3 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.88 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.43 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7629.42 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632.67 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.86 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.33 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7623 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7622.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.56 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.14 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7620.27 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7625.49 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7623.46 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7623.5 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.03 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7625.03 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7621.19 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7625.76 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.47 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.47 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627.04 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7626.52 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.06 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7627.73 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7628.2 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7632 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.46 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.26 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.6 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.47 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.11 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.44 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630.02 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7630 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.08 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.39 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7639.84 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7639.96 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7636.56 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7634.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7634.22 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7637.38 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7631.05 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7624.8 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.39 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.4 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.39 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7635.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7655.83 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7668.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7665.08 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7654.95 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7651.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7655.91 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7652.54 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7649.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7655.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7658.57 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7653 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7653 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7656 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7659.18 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7653.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7654.51 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7650.51 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7651.61 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7654.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7655.73 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7660 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7660 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7658.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7658.01 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7660.2 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7652.05 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7651.6 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7646.34 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7643 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7645.79 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7645.97 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7642.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7646.25 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7645.26 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7641.61 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7644 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7642.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7642.14 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7640.32 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7639.62 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7637.9 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7637 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7633.48 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7625.12 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7608.31 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7608.31 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7560 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7543.19 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7547.91 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7539.95 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7521.31 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7524.81 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7515.69 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7510.59 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7520 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7530 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7529.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7531.49 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7530 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7530.99 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7532 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7533.98 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7531.12 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7529 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7520 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7519.22 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7518.24 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7488.3 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7498.00000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7505.52000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7504.94000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7505.00000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7507.30000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7513.82000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7514.82000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7519.00000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7516.99000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7516.99000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7512.10000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7510.79000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7510.27000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7511.00000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7512.06000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7514.60000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7515.00000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Minimum price change not reached. Price need to be below 7382.3984 USDT. Current price: 7518.84000000 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Backtest Results:</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM ============================</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Applied Fee Percentage: 0%</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Total Profits: 0.0 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Total Fee Costs: 0 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Total Gain: 0.0 USDT</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM Return On Investment: 0</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:16 PM ============================</string>
    <string>6/6/2018 7:12:18 PM Trade amount warning. Your wallet says you have 0.00429644 BTC while you require 0.134 BTC to trade.</string>
  </BotLogBook>
  <CompletedOrders>
    <BaseOrder xsi:type="ExchangeOrder">
      <OrderId>ba42d6b8-574d-4953-8027-36f6a22119c4</OrderId>
      <OrderStatus>Completed</OrderStatus>
      <OrderStatusAsString>Completed</OrderStatusAsString>
      <OrderType>Sell</OrderType>
      <OrderTypeAsString>Sell</OrderTypeAsString>
      <PriceType>Limit</PriceType>
      <PriceTypeAsString>Limit</PriceTypeAsString>
      <Amount>0.134</Amount>
      <AmountFilled>0.0</AmountFilled>
      <Price>7610.72</Price>
      <FeePercentage>0</FeePercentage>
      <FeeCosts>0</FeeCosts>
      <Profits>0.0</Profits>
      <Notes />
      <Origin />
      <DependsOn />
      <IsExecutingAsId />
      <AddedTime>2018-06-05T17:39:00</AddedTime>
      <UnixAddedTime>1528220340</UnixAddedTime>
      <LastUpdate>2018-06-05T17:39:00</LastUpdate>
      <UnixLastUpdate>1528220340</UnixLastUpdate>
      <TimeoutInMinutes>15</TimeoutInMinutes>
      <Platform>Sandbox</Platform>
      <Pair>
        <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
        <SecondaryCurrency>USDT</SecondaryCurrency>
      </Pair>
    </BaseOrder>
  </CompletedOrders>
  <IsOrderStopLossActive>false</IsOrderStopLossActive>
  <PlatformType>SpotTrading</PlatformType>
  <CoinPosition>Sold</CoinPosition>
  <FundsPosition>NoPosition</FundsPosition>
  <CurrentTradeAmount>0.134</CurrentTradeAmount>
  <CorrectedTradeAmount>0.0</CorrectedTradeAmount>
  <LastBuyPrice>0.0</LastBuyPrice>
  <LastSellPrice>7610.72</LastSellPrice>
  <CappedSeconds>5</CappedSeconds>
  <Interval>1</Interval>
  <StopLoss>0</StopLoss>
  <StopLossPrice>7948.650</StopLossPrice>
  <DisableAfterStopLoss>false</DisableAfterStopLoss>
  <PriceChangeToBuy>3</PriceChangeToBuy>
  <PriceChangeToSell>5</PriceChangeToSell>
  <PriceChangeTarget>7382.3984</PriceChangeTarget>
  <Macd>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>1</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Buy</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Fast</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>41</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Slow</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>130</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MACD Signal</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>500</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>41</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <MacdFast>41</MacdFast>
    <MacdSlow>130</MacdSlow>
    <MacdSign>41</MacdSign>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </Macd>
  <BBands>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>1</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Stay</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Length</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>1</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>50</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Dev.Up</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0.00001</Min>
        <Max>999.9</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,2})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.01</Step>
        <Value>1.86</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Dev.Down</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0.00001</Min>
        <Max>999.9</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,2})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.01</Step>
        <Value>1.94</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>MA Type</Title>
        <FieldType>optionlist</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>Kama</Value>
        <Options>
          <string>Sma</string>
          <string>Ema</string>
          <string>Wma</string>
          <string>Dema</string>
          <string>Tema</string>
          <string>Trima</string>
          <string>Kama</string>
          <string>Mama</string>
          <string>T3</string>
        </Options>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Deviation</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>0</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Require FCC</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Reset Middle</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Allow Mid Sells</Title>
        <FieldType>boolean</FieldType>
        <Min>0.0</Min>
        <Max>0.0</Max>
        <Pattern />
        <Step>0.0</Step>
        <Value>False</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <Length>50</Length>
    <Devup>1.86</Devup>
    <Devdn>1.94</Devdn>
    <MaType>Kama</MaType>
    <ResetMid>false</ResetMid>
    <AllowMidSell>false</AllowMidSell>
    <RequireFcc>false</RequireFcc>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </BBands>
  <Rsi>
    <IndicatorType>Aroon</IndicatorType>
    <PriceMarket>
      <PrimaryCurrency>BTC</PrimaryCurrency>
      <SecondaryCurrency>DEMO1</SecondaryCurrency>
      <ContractName />
      <PriceSource>Sandbox</PriceSource>
      <PriceMarketType>Forex</PriceMarketType>
    </PriceMarket>
    <ChartType>CandlestickHLC</ChartType>
    <Timer>1</Timer>
    <ChartStepping>1.0</ChartStepping>
    <Deviation>0</Deviation>
    <StandAlone>false</StandAlone>
    <InBenchmark>false</InBenchmark>
    <BetaStage>false</BetaStage>
    <UseBuySignals>true</UseBuySignals>
    <UseSellSignals>true</UseSellSignals>
    <UseLongSignals>true</UseLongSignals>
    <UseNoPositionSignals>true</UseNoPositionSignals>
    <UseShortSignals>true</UseShortSignals>
    <ReverseSignals>false</ReverseSignals>
    <BuySellResult>Stay</BuySellResult>
    <ShortLongResult>NoPosition</ShortLongResult>
    <MappedLongSignal>Long</MappedLongSignal>
    <MappedShortSignal>Short</MappedShortSignal>
    <IndicatorInterface>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Length</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>1</Min>
        <Max>999999</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+</Pattern>
        <Step>1</Step>
        <Value>2</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Buy level</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>100</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,1})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.1</Step>
        <Value>9</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
      <IndicatorField>
        <Title>Sell level</Title>
        <FieldType>number</FieldType>
        <Min>0</Min>
        <Max>100</Max>
        <Pattern>[0-9]+([.\,][0-9]{1,1})?</Pattern>
        <Step>0.1</Step>
        <Value>69</Value>
      </IndicatorField>
    </IndicatorInterface>
    <RsiLength>2</RsiLength>
    <RsiOversold>9</RsiOversold>
    <RsiOverbought>69</RsiOverbought>
    <Rsi>48.8322650979698</Rsi>
    <LastRsi>23.9394712142336</LastRsi>
    <SupportedBotTypes>
      <enumBotType>TradeBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>MarginBot</enumBotType>
      <enumBotType>LeverageBot</enumBotType>
    </SupportedBotTypes>
  </Rsi>
  <UseTwoSignals>true</UseTwoSignals>
</MadHatterBot>